worldtimeserver.com 2019-12-08

# WorldTimeServer.com Privacy Policy

At WorldTimeServer.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit WorldTimeServer.com, and how we safeguard your information.

Above all, we want you to know that we never sell your personal information to third parties!

####    
Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Verizon), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

The information in our log files is used simply to monitor our WorldTimeServer.com web site to both ensure it is performing as we expect and to help troubleshoot any problems when they crop up.

####    
Cookies and Web Beacons

We use first-party cookies from WorldTimeServer.com to store information, but this information is limited to just what is needed to remember your personal preferences when you visit our site.

We also use third party advertisements on WorldTimeServer.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in security/antivirus/firewall programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Google has a privacy policy for the Google Ads which run on WorldTimeServer.com, which you can review at <http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html> . Google is using a DoubleClick cookie on Adsense partner sites like WorldTimeServer.com, but if you would like to opt-out, you will find instructions in the Google privacy policy.

####    
Contact Us

We have asked our adverisers to not use pop-ups, pop-unders or interstitial pages, as we find them as annoying as you do! Advertising, however, does provide the funding to keep WorldTimeServer.com up and running for everyone.

If you have any questions about this policy, feel free to Contact Us or write us at:

WorldTimeServer.com  
925 N Illinois Route 3, Suite 105  
Waterloo, IL 62298  
United States

####    
Effective Date

This policy statement was originally created and put into effect on April 15, 2015. 

This policy is based on principles followed by our company since our founding in 1991.
